[{"answer": "Vacation", "docId": "Forrest-Gump.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Vacation's when you go somewhere, and you don't ever come back", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "my friend! I told you not to bother this nice young man", "docId": "Forrest-Gump.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "All right, but your supper's ready if y'all want to eat", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "This is the bus to school", "docId": "Forrest-Gump.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I'm my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "And next to Momma, no one ever talked to me or asked me questions", "docId": "Forrest-Gump.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Mommy says stupid is as stupid does", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend, what's going on", "docId": "Forrest-Gump.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "my friend? When raccoons try to get on our back porch, Momma just chase 'em off with a broom", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "My bus is here", "docId": "Forrest-Gump.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No, it's the number 4", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I didn't ask you to pull me out of there, goddamn you! What the hell do you think you're going", "docId": "Forrest-Gump.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I got an air strike inbound right now. They're gonna nape the whole area", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "That's all I have to say about that", "docId": "Forrest-Gump.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "A bullet", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "For some reason, ping pong came very natural to me", "docId": "Forrest-Gump.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "So I started playing it all the time", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Tell us a little bit about the war, man", "docId": "Forrest-Gump.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "The war in Vie", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "No problem", "docId": "Forrest-Gump.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Good night", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Okay, so I was wrong", "docId": "Forrest-Gump.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Well, maybe you should just pray for shrimp", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "my friend, go my friend", "docId": "Forrest-Gump.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yeah, well you'll have to tell them to call him back. He is indisposed at the moment", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "And then, she was there", "docId": "Forrest-Gump.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Hello, my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Why, you don't need to take a bus. my friend is just five or six blocks down that way", "docId": "Forrest-Gump.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Down that way", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "my friend, I'm sick", "docId": "Forrest-Gump.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I have some kind virus. And the doctors don't, they don't know what it is. And there isn't anything they can do about it", "qsentId": 32}]